Hollywood Dirt is a drama, romance film directed by Tosca Musk.
Hollywood arrives in force to Quincy, the small town where
the secret Crown Cola billionaire's live.
They want to film about the billionaire's and how they made their fortunes.
Summer Jenkins, who was the town pariah, joins forces with the scout, Ben, and finds filming
locations, extras, lessons with the town officials and house owners, etc.
When Cole Masten arrives, they hate each other, but sparks fly.
Cole is running from a nasty divorce, yet is captivated by Summer.
Summer is dying to leave town to get away from the gossip.
This is a great story about Southern customs, a Southern
girl, and a Hollywood star who finds his lady.
Summer Jenkins, played by Emma Rigby.
Cole Masten, played by Johann Urb.
Thelma, played by Mindy Cohn.
Brad DeLuca, played by Marco Dapper.
Stacy, played by Melissa LeEllen.
Mama, played by Beverly Leech.
The Dirt is a 2019 American biographical comedy-drama film directed by Jeff Tremaine and written
by Rich Wilkes and Amanda Adelson, about heavy metal/glam metal band Mötley Crüe.
The film stars Douglas Booth, Colson Baker, Daniel Webber and Iwan Rheon.
Talks of a Mötley Crüe biopic began as early as 2006, when Paramount Pictures and MTV Films purchased the rights to the book The Dirt: Confessions of the World's Most Notorious Rock Band by the band and
Neil Strauss; however, the project then languished in development hell for over a decade, going through numerous directors and cast members before Netflix purchased the rights in March 2017.
Filming began around New Orleans in February 2018.
The Dirt was released digitally on Netflix on March 22, 2019.
It received generally negative reviews from critics, who said the film would please fans but
that it hesitated "in handling the more troubling aspects of the band's history."
The tone is emotional.